<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<dbEntries type="Lands">
	<entry>
		<name>Hegos Plains</name>
		<description>Hegos Plains, named after famous advocate of terraforming - Arthur Hegos, were the first regions to be discovered. In these areas no bigger terrain diversity is to be found. The height amplitude is relatively narrow resulting in almost flat areas. On plains many herbs may be found, but only wise mind will appreciate and make use of them. Hegos Plains are home to many animals. Some of them are dangerous but in many cases its better to run away or hide.

The climate here is bearable for humans, even without a special suit. During spring the temperature shifts from 7 degrees Celsius to 18. Summertime is much more pleasant for most people, reaching temperatures between 15 and 36 degrees Celsius. When over half of year is past, outdoor condition start to become less friendly. Rain is more common sight and it's generally colder reaching between 2 and 8 degrees Celsius. Near the year's end winter brings the lowest temperatures you can experience here. They drop even to -18 degrees Celsius, and at best conditions temperatures reach up to -3 degrees Celsius.</description>
        <inhabitancies></inhabitancies>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Gedo Desert</name>
        <description>Such a harsh environment can only be home to the fittest organisms. However many animals are accustomed to extreme temperatures and dry air. The ability to protect yourself from those creatures can make the difference between life nad death. It might be challenging, but many treasures may be found in these dry lands.

Unfortunate location creates a climate unbearable for humans without any protection. Tempeatures here reach enormous values during whole year. A norm is between 50 and 110 degrees Celsius.</description>
        <inhabitancies></inhabitancies>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Aurora Forest</name>
        <description>Name "Aurora" was formed by explorer Yuto Yamashita, who was a space nomad, after he described variety of colours that can be seen there even from orbit during all seasons. Aurora has condensed wildlife which shares this small area as its home. Therefore any explorer must be very cautious because danger can come from any direction and in various forms.

Terrain on which Aurora Forest has grown is very uneven. There are many hills and sometimes even small cliffs. Agile person can climb them easily because of many rocks and roots sticking out of them.

Due to its rather southern location climate here is warmer than in forests on the north. Tempeatures between 14 and 25 degrees Celsius are characteristic to spring. Next months bring new amounts of hot air from south increasing average tempereatures by 10 degrees Celsius. As the September ends, temperatures start their slow deacrease to reach values similar to spring ones. Winter is definitely the coolest period in year cicle in Aurora Forest, but it is still bearable for human. At that time temperatures tend to reach from 6 to 10 degrees Celsius.</description>
        <inhabitancies></inhabitancies>
	</entry>
</dbEntries>
