<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<dbEntries type="Mercenaries">
    <entry>
		<name>Adam Anderson</name>
		<description>Born on metropolis ship ACX-12 in 2089 Adam spent most of his life there. Despite his parents who wanted him to become engineer, Adam dreamed of adventurous life since the early years. At school he always hanged out with bullies. Such companions made him tough and accutomed to fights. Adam Anderson is a rather frail person but years spent in communities in which the strongest ruled, taught him to defend himself and care for own gains.

After reaching adulthood Adam escaped from home and after few days of wandering alone, he left his mothership and was hired on spacejunk collector where he worked as a guard. After quitting his first job, Adam traveled through space trying to earn a living. These years weren't wasted. Experience he gained helped him become a professional bounty hunter.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>Agda Solberg</name>
	<description>Agda Solberg was born in 2099 on Xeres314 - one of the moons of Jupiter54, in mining colony that belonged to United Engineers' Group. Both her parents, working as engineers, made sure that thier daughter would inherit intelligence thanks to genotype creation control. Agda is indeed above average in terms of intelligence. However something must have gone not according to plan. Despite the possibilities that life gave her, she prefer phisical activity, traveling and discovering. Therefore she joined the Space Nomads. It's a group of people, whose desire is to explore the unknown places in space.

Her parents were dissatisfied to say at least. Despite their emotions Agda's choice was respected. After long recrutation period, the girl has been accepted and officialy has been greeted in Space Nomads community. Since then, she has been wandering through space looking for unusual places and occurrences.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Alan Clark</name>
		<description>Alan's past isn't known and he would like it to stay like this. Everything that we could find is the fact that he propably was born in sector Ac13.

Clark doesn't look like a criminal. He isn't aggressive nor strong. However Alan Clark is way above average intelligent. Fully aware of that he took advantage of any occasion life gave him despite of legal issues.

Alan Clark has visited many prisons. One of the most famous crimes he was enprisoned for is hijacking a battlecruiser for local gang. He even managed to escape from infamous La Puerta del Diablo, one of the strictest prison camps that is believed to be impossible to escape from.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Alex Freeman</name>
		<description>Alex Freeman was born in 2102 on Anteria, a planet similar to Earth that was colonised at the 70's of XXI century. His parents were obsessed with technology. Because of that, when augmentation has become appeared on commercial market, his father bought him many modifications. Alan's performance has increased without a doubt. Everything was fine until 2123. At that time Freeman was studying at university. Meanwhile the policital conflict on Anteria was rising. Two groups self calling Probots and Robophobes that had been fighting for many years started riots that created chaos on whole Anteria. During that time augmented people were minority. Goverment was helpless and after many years and many lifes taken. Their last desperate move was poll in which people could vote for or against cybernetic equality. Sadly, robophobes had their numbers and dominated probots. The cyber holocaust had begun. Most of the augmented ones were killed, including Alex's parents. The rest were enprisoned. After 7 years of living in extreme conditions, all probots who were still alive organised and assaulted prison were augmented people were kept. This attack was succesful and the last augs had left their motherland.

Since the great escape Alex has been travelling getting various jobs, but none of them has given him what he was seeking.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Steven Brown</name>
		<description>Steven Brown born in quite wealth family in christmas eve, in 2090. Lost his mother in the age of 6 years . His only wish was to become an archeologist like his father, who was the greatest „authorithet” and teacher for him. Since childhood, he was travelling a lot, so he had numerous occasions to meet new people around the whole galaxy. Moreover, his optymism made him a great companion, especially to drink.  As the efect, he has a lot of useful contacts.

Nowadayes he earn money in any ethical way to suport his family (district where he was registered, lost almost everything after crisis in 2139).  Having a various expirience, Steven Brown can be a proper material for any interesting expedition.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Anna Tyler</name>
		<description>As a toddler sold on the black market, she was taken to a research center connected with illegal experiments on alive beings. The purpose of the panel was to refine „efficiency” of humans, basing on an endocrine-disrupting specifics, especially those increasing level of adrenaline.

In 2113, a massacre happened in the research center. The only alive witness is Anna, however, how small, petite girl could kill seven adult men hasn’t been explained till today. After the tragedy, media took this subject up so there was no way to continue research.

Then, the Priests of the Universe took over charge of her. This organization exerted a crucial influence on her late life. She has been taking part in the devotions in the middle of the  forest so often, that meditation outdoors became her favourite activity.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Brian Cartner</name>
		<description>One of the last people born on Earth, spent his childhood on metropolis ship ACX–13. He was the top student at school, however he didn’t graduate from college because of difficult family situation (his parents were shot in famed terrorist attack on third district of his metropolis ship, in 2092). On account of the tragedy, he had to take care of his younger sister. After she reached maturity, they quarreled. Since today, siblings have no contact with each other.

However Brian was quite strong and despite of straitened circumstances, he has never given up . Having extensive general knowledge, especially technical and considerable physical endurance, he gained a lot of experience while working in various places. Brian is well–known owing to his lack of luck – he was a participant to many accidents, three times married (nowadays he feels slight aversion to women). Despite of this, he’s well-thought-of and quite cheerfull. Usually extroverted and outgoing, however he avoids the topic of the origin deep scar on his arm.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Evan Turner</name>
		<description>Evan, born on the Df13 b, as a young boy was used to the view of machinery and dullness. Before his first travel, young Turner was concerned, that in the future he will not stand out of average Anterians. He felt neither exhiliration, nor sadness about that, just that’s how (as he thought) it should be.

Suddenly in 2103 he unexpectedly won a small contest. The reward was a trip to Df13 d, which he had visited few months later. This planet is quite famous for having an untouched ecosystem and being official, interplanetary nature preserve. This place completely changed him. He became fascinated with the beauty of the universe and decided to completely alter his life.

Till today, he enjoys the most spending time near the nature as well as trying to be as joyful as possible all the time. Evan get to do odd jobs, only when he has to, and more likely he will choose the one which doesn’t require having a brush with others. Even though not being antisocial, he definitely avoids contact with the people, who can’t understand him.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Zofia Wysocka</name>
		<description>Born in the one of the wealthest part of the De15 system. Zofia’s family is commonly known for having undeniable influence on the interplanetary economy and connections with Terran’s mafia. Because of her noticed early amazing talents and ability to learn quickly, since childhood she has been educating and training, to take family buisness over. However, Zofia had another plans for herself.

It is quite possible, that due to strict upbringing, she has always valued freedom and independence. Her mindset and no will to achieve a compromise resulted in being exiled from her family. However Zofia, always confident and adamant, didn’t pay a lot of attention to this matter.

It isn’t surely known what has been happening with her for the next years. It is believed, that Zofia Wysocka may be a genuine identity of a well–known assasin from ACX–03, however this connection has never been proven. All that is known, is a fact, that she has spent a lot of time and money in a little tavern on the Df13–c, famous for extremely diverse customers. There, Zofia often gladly undertakes risky jobs, however only when it’s worth it.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Paul Luft</name>
		<description>He grew up with other Gunzerkers, on a metropolis ship ACX-002, parents unknown. From childhood, he has been showing physical prowess, which was later artificially reinforced. Therefore he is an ideal candidate for any dirty work, but it should be mentioned, that nature hasn’t been generous in his intelligence.

Sometimes quite nervous, he can do everything to achieve his goal. It can be both a strength and weakness. However, after prevalence of droids, Paul as an every Gunzerker found it difficult to get hired. Nowadays he’s ready to undertake any job to earn some money.

However he isn’t villainous, quite the opposite, Paul has a heart of gold. This is especially visible due to his relationship with Sam, a boy whom he saved from his drunk father. Paul felt that it was his moral duty to help him in any way. Nowadays they still keep in touch.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Juan Mercado</name>
		<description>Juan in the childhood had been sent to the military school belonged to the Terran Republic. There, he gained the skill of rapid regeneration and got the basic education. His mother was raising him alone, and believed that achieving leadership in the army is the best way for a boy to settle down. After loosing her husband, she tried her best to make a real man out of her son. She was strict and was resorting to viloence on himwhen he was disobedient to make him tough. In result, Juan was afraid not only of his mother, but also of the generally difficult situations. Unfortunately, his talent for making excuses only intensified his cowardly nature.

A few years later when mother died, he decided to abandon the army and join the cult of pantheists. He engaged that much, he was chosen to be the Priest of the Universe. The majority of the time, he is contemplating nature and the miracle of life. After choosing the new way of life, Juan dealt with his trauma.</description>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<name>Oksana Syriotuk</name>
		<description>Born as Olivier Syriotuk, on ACX–09. As a child very timid and nervous. Quite talented, however he never used to exhibit self–confidence. His character fitted into his look. Oliver was scraggy and rather short. Loved by parents, they granted him the best possible education on their mothership. Despite that he has always been the same: reserved, hating to be in the spotlight. This changed after Oliver’s first visit to Cha&amp;G, a company, which as a pioneer introduced a total sex change surgery on the market.

It was a fulfilling of his daydream. Oliver could finally feel good in his own body. Obviously, this kind of operations isn’t as popular as in 90’s, however the whole situation wasn’t very surprising for all his acquaintances and family. Changing a name to Oksana was only a formality. 

Nowadays, Oksana in no way reminds her old version. She is a very extroverted and energetic person, who likes adventures and doesn’t contemn a risk. Taking this into consideration, Oksana may be a proper candidate for any interesting jobs.</description>
	</entry>
</dbEntries>
